# Ifeoluwase Adeleke

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Profile**

Full-stack engineer with over 2years work experience able to build responsive web applications from the ground up. Proficient with HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript. Hands on experience with CSS frameworks like Bootstrap and Materialize. I have experience in building responsive apps with JavaScript frameworks like EJS, React.js, Next.js and quality REST APIs with Nodejs and Express.js. I also write Technical Articles on different programming topics on Medium.

## **Employment History**

#### Junior Software Engineer, Ancla Technologies, Yaba, Lagos

APRIL 2022 — NOVEMBER 2022

- Led weekly meetings with clients and in-house staff to go over websites progress reports.
- Managed Obade web app and built new features within time constraints that currently serve over 1000 users.
- Collaborated to create strategic initiatives to design, code, and test solutions.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Worked with React Native to convert figma designs to mobile apps to create new software updates for VetroPay.

#### Software Engineer (contract), Konnect.ws, Remote

SEPTEMBER 2021 — MARCH 2022

- Worked to build competing website in regards to content, look, and feel with React.js
- Planned software architecture and built Rest API on the back-end with Nodejs using Sequelize as ORM and MySQL as Database.
- Integration of third-party payment systems such as Flutterwave and Paystack.
- Integration of third-party APIs for file storage and website feature implementation.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web application.
- Effectively multi-tasked and worked well with internal and external teams.

#### Website Developer, Kescreative, Ikotun, Lagos State

APRIL 2021 — JANUARY 2022

- Collaborated with a team of creatives to develop a now defunct edu-tech website using React.js.
- Developed a Rest API with Nodejs and Mongoose to service over 175 school pupils watching tutorials.
- Tested, deployed, and maintained web application on Namecheap and cPanel.

## **Education**

#### **Details**

5, Sanusi Street, Council bus stop, Ikotun, Lagos, 102213, Nigeria 08132277316 eadelekeife@gmail.com

#### **Technical Skills**

HTML5 & CSS3

**JavaScript** 

React.js

Node.js

**React Native** 

MongoDB / MySQL

jQuery

Git / GitHub / BitBucket

Sequelize / Mongoose

Bootstrap / SASS

Ant Design / Materialize

SQL

## Languages

English

Yoruba

#### Links

My Portfolio

GitHub

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Medium

Twitter

#### **Hobbies**

Playing and watching Football, Travelling, Writing Articles, Listening to Music, Watching Stage Performances.

#### BSc Chemistry, Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta,

OCTOBER 2017 — FEBRUARY 2023

## SSCE, Sigma Bond Academy, Ikotun, Lagos State

JANUARY 2011 — MAY 2014

#### **Courses**

#### Code with Node JS - 2021, Udemy

FEBRUARY 2021 — MAY 2021

#### Modern React with Redux, Udemy

OCTOBER 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

## The Modern JavaScript Bootcamp Course (2020), Udemy

MAY 2020 — JULY 2020

## Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS, Udemy

APRIL 2020 — APRIL 2020

## Web Design for Web Developers: Build Beautiful Websites, Udemy

APRIL 2020

# Internships

#### Frontend Engineer at Titan Galaxy, Abeokuta

OCTOBER 2020 — APRIL 2021

- Helped to build and add new features to FunaabPay website
- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.
- · Helped to build and upload new client websites

#### References

References available upon request